Welcome to discourse about react it's great to have you on board.
Tepki verici sylemlere ho geldiniz, sizi gemide grmek harika.
My name is on Schwartz Molla and I'm a freelance web developer.
Benim adm Schwartz Molla ve ben serbest web gelitiricisiyim.
Andrew yeck developer I worked with re-act a lot and I can tell you it's an amazing library for creating
Andrew yeck gelitiricisi ok tekrar altm ve ok esnek ve son derece hzl javascript
highly reactive and super fast javascript driven web applications the javascript driven part is especially
tahrikli web uygulamalar oluturmak iin artc bir kitaplk olduunu syleyebilirim, nk Riak bir javascript kitaplndan bu yana
important because since Riak is a javascript library it's of course about writing your web apps in javascript
tabii ki yazma hakknda ok nemli olan javascript odakl web uygulamalar nemlidir. web uygulamalarnz
and that in turn is amazing because since javascript runs in the browser it allows you to create superfast
javascript iinde ve artc nk javascript taraycda altrld iin mobil uygulamalar gibi sper hzl
web apps that feel like mobile apps.
web uygulamalar oluturmanza olanak salyor.
Users don't have to wait for Peytral loads.
Kullanclar Peytral yklerini beklemek zorunda deiller.
Now re-act is probably the most popular javascript library you can learn these days.
imdi re-act muhtemelen bu gn renebileceiniz en popler javascript kitapldr.
And for a good reason you will learn all of its core features from this course and way more than that
Ve iyi bir nedenden dolay, temel zelliklerinin tmn bu ders ve yollardan
you will learn what reactor's about how it works and why you might want to use it.
reneceksiniz, ne reaktrn alt ve neden onu kullanmak istediinizi reneceksiniz.
You will learn how to build components would react how to use read X for better state management how
Bileenlerin nasl oluturulacan reneceksiniz, daha iyi devlet ynetimi iin d okunuunu nasl kullanacanza tepki
to use d react router and you'll not just learned as simple projects or theory.
gstereceini ve ynlendirici ynlendirmeyi nasl kullanacanz reneceksiniz ve sadece basit projeler veya teori olarak reneceksiniz.
No we will build an entire re-act application throughout this course.
Hayr, bu ders boyunca tekrar tekrar uygulama bavurusu yapmayacaz.
The Bergere Boulder which is an amazing application utilizing all the concepts you learn in this course
Bu ders boyunca rendiiniz tm kavramlar kullanan inanlmaz bir uygulama olan Bergere Boulder,
so that you have a really solid understanding of all the concepts taught throughout this course.
bylece bu ders boyunca retilen tm kavramlar gerekten salam bir anlaya sahip olacaksnz.
By the end of the Course you'll therefore have way more than just a solid understanding of react and
Kursun sonunda bu nedenle kat bir reaksiyon tepkisinden baka bir yol bulacaksnz ve
you'll be able to dive deeper into more challenging projects and apply for reactive Alper chops or become
daha zorlu projelere daha fazla girip reaksiyon gsteren Alper pirinleri iin bavurabilir veya bir Riak
a Riak developer.
gelitiricisi olabilirsiniz.
As a freelancer Whatever your goal is.
Freelancer olarak amacnz ne olursa olsun.